Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION.
Are Constantinopolis' treasures are not enough
that you came all this way for treasure?
Don't talk too much, woman!
Don't touch her!
My Bey...
... neither Dündar Bey, nor
Gündüz Bey would let this go.
Brother Boran! Everyone, every
person in this Tent will know this.
Whoever betrays Osman,
son of Ertuğrul Gazi...
... their end would be like this.
If I had kept my silence
after this treason today...
... how could I walk in here,
calling myself a soldier, an Alp?
If I hadn't punished
my uncle's son, Batur...
... my own kin...
... If I separate traitors as
"ours" or "theirs" tomorrow...
... would my father's efforts and...
... my mother's milk be halal?
- You are right
- You are right, my Bey.
We'd give our lives for
your justice, for your way.
Now, what are we going to do, my Bey?
I didn't spill all this
blood for nothing, Konuralp.
If anyone, not just my brother or my uncle,
stands in our way, they will share the same fate.
Everyone will be sure of it.
- My son, my valiant.
- He tried to kill me, mother.
- He wanted me dead.
- Nothing's going to happen to you, my valiant.
Don't you worry, your mother's
blessed hands will make you better.
He wanted to kill me,
mother, he tried to kill me.
Bring those clothes now, Burçin!
Will my brother be okay, mother?
The fate of a Kayı woman is determined
with blood. This is no time to cry.
Take these clothes and wash them.
Get up, come on! Hurry.
Burçin, pour some hemp milk on the daisy.
And don't forget to boil the giant fennel.
I will, mother Zöhre.
Aygül, make an oven here.
Blacksmith.
You know about the quarrel
with the castle, we are on alert.
I also commanded men to
bring their weapons to you.
- Take a look at them.
- Yes, Gündüz Bey.
I don't want laziness in the Tent, you should
know that. Everyone needs to do their job now.
- Yes, my Bey.
- Can I come in my Bey?
Come.
- Gündüz Bey.
- What? What happened to you?
- Osman Bey.
- What happened to Osman Bey?
Osman bey stabbed Batur
in front of Dündar Bey's tent!
Osman, may your hands never hold a shield,
may your chest fill with blood, Osman!
If I become a traitor like your son...
-... may it be like you said, aunt.
- Haven't you got enough blood?
Is it my son, Batur's turn, after Aybars?
You know...
... we wash life with life, and blood with
blood! Let go of my hand, Gündüz Bey!
Do you want injustice, or justice, aunt?
Let go of my hand.
I want revenge, Gündüz Bey.
Why is your voice so high, Zöhre Hatun?
Aren't there men left in your tent?
This is not over yet, Osman.
You spilled my own blood.
If you wanted to take
my son away from me...
... then you will pay for it!
You've done this too, Osman?
You've done this too, at last.
Enough of this, Osman!
When will you stand still?
When will you calm down?
Your brother will calm down
when the treachery ends, brother!
No, you won't come to your senses, Osman.
You won't learn.
Alps!
Put Osman Bey in the cage!
Treason, or being a part of treason.
There is no difference for me, Gündüz Bey!
I am obeying the law because you are the
Commander, not because you are my brother.
I will confront you for all this too.
You should know that.
My son.
Son, fighting like a lion with mane...
... when he didn't even have a
mustache as big as his eyebrows.
Son, standing up like a banner...
... when he falls.
You made this black earth your home...
... oh, my son!
Son, no, you are not dead.
Doesn't the One who created
these lands and the sky say so?
- Surah Al-Baqarah [2:154]
"Rather, they are alive,
but you perceive [it] not."
We don't perceive it, son, we don't.
But...
... the ones who will come
after you will know it.
They will know, son.
Son, if you don't fall...
... If I don't fall...
... how could this, this black
earth become our homeland?
How could this black earth
become our homeland?
What is it, Erkutalp,
why are you in a rush?
My Bey, Osman Bey stabbed Batur
in front of Dündar Bey's tent.
What are you talking about, Erkutalp?
What are you talking about?
Come on, come on! Come on!
Forgive us, my Bey.
- Whatever the command says.
- Everyone should do their duties first.
No one should be upset because
of their duties, my brothers.
Bring the goods!
So, you are thirsty. Huh?
You won't even get a sip
of it before you talk.
- Bamsı Bey.
- My Osman!
- Why, my valiant?
- Every treason has consequences.
And Batur paid the consequences
of his treason!
Good, good then, he got what he deserved.
But Osman, what is that treason? Tell me.
They handed over Theokoles, the biggest
leverage that would lead us to...
... my brother, Aybar's
killers, to the castle.
Who did this, my Osman,
who could've done this to us?
My uncle, my brother...
... Batur.
Whose blood is this?
Osman Bey attacked Batur, my Bey.
Zöhre Hatuns are treating him inside.
Lion of his father, my Batur.
You will get better, my
son, you will get better.
He tried to kill me, father.
Osman has spilled our blood.
Where is this Osman hiding now?
- Where is he?
- He is neither hiding nor afraid.
He is Osman, he implied that he
did good, while looking at my eyes.
He will suffer the consequences
of spilling Dündar Bey's son's blood!
Father, stop him...
... or he will be the end of us.
Dündar Bey!
Gündüz put him in a cage. Being
his uncle is finished now, Dündar Bey.
Let Osman see your Bey
face too from now on.
I will show Osman what is the
meaning of spilling blood now.
I will show him.
What were you doing while
Osman was stabbing my son?
What were you doing?
Dündar Bey!
What were you thinking, Dündar Bey!
How could you give the bait that would
help us find Aybar's killers, Dündar Bey!
How could you hand him over to the castle?
So that there won't be any more sorrows.
So that valiants like Aybars won't fall.
So that we don't fight
with the Byzantine while...
... the Mongols try to come at us.
So that we keep our Tent alive
until my brother comes back, Bamsı Bey!
But, what has changed after we did that?
Osman Bey, the great warrior of Kayı,
sneaked inside and killed him anyway.
Open your ears now, Bamsı Bey,
Osman is the one who killed Theokoles!
He almost killed my Batur,
if it wasn't for the people.
He almost ripped my heart out.
Dündar Bey, my Osman's courage, my
Osman's strength has broken your balance!
You blame Osman for everything!
From Yorgopolos' death to Theokoles'
murder, every lead is pointing Osman.
Don't you cast a shadow on Kayı's
future by joining Osman's party!
Open your eyes! See the truth yourself!
Do you know what I see when I open my
eyes and look at you, Dündar Bey?
Do you know what I see?
Laziness, I see laziness
when I look at you!
Not laziness, it's caution,
Bamsı Bey, it's caution.
Bithynia's balance is like scales.
I won't let Osman do as he pleases
and hurt people's lives anymore!
You will see, I won't let him.
Osman is my Ertuğrul Bey's entrusted!
I won't let you touch Osman, Dündar Bey!
I won't let you!
We didn't find this Tent on
a road, Bamsı Bey! I...
... am Dündar, son of Süleyman Şah!
Even if, not even Osman,
my own son who is struggling...
... for his life inside tries
to harm Kayı's future...
... I won't show mercy, I will destroy!
While I, Bamsı Beyrek...
... am alive, no one will ever
be able to touch Osman!
I will swallow fury, Dündar Bey!
I will breathe blood!
I will spit fire, I will burn everywhere,
Dündar Bey! I will burn everywhere...
... everywhere, Dündar Bey!
My Bey, pardon me, an
important event has occurred.
What happened?
They attacked the New Bazaar,
my Bey, they slaughtered everyone.
What did you say? Inform Gündüz Bey
at once, we are going to the New Bazaar.
- Now!
- Yes, my Bey.
When I return, I will confront that Osman.
I will.
You get out.
You got your hands bloody today, Osman.
You spilled the blood of
your own kind today, Osman!
Tell me now, what will this lead to?
What will this action lead to?
I spilled the blood that was poisoning
Kayıs from the inside, brother!
This is just a start.
Don't you ever make
a mistake too, from now on.
I am not Batur, Osman.
Did you hear me? I am not Batur!
I will carve the eyes of the man
who draws a sword on me!
Know your place!
Otherwise, I won't say "My brother"...
I won't wait for my father...
... I will rip your heart out
with my own hands, Osman!
Everything is clear, both
blindness and treason!
You should be afraid, not me!
Osman...
... while you were still
crying on your cradle...
... I was learning
politics from my father.
The purpose is what
matters, Osman. That means...
... sometimes various foul plays
are needed for conquest! That means...
... someone naive as you
can't comprehend these games!
Gündüz Bey, New Bazaar has been attacked,
Dündar Bey is calling for you at once...
... they will be going
there with the Alps.
Bala Hatun.
Brother...
... unlock my hands.
So you can put us
in more trouble, Osman?
Unlock my hands! I need to
get to New Bazaar at once!
Tell me that first...
... what is your business in this?
Why do you care about New Bazaar?
Brother!
You first think about how you are going
to protect yourself from that infidel, Kalonoz.
Brother! Brother, unlock my hands!
Unlock me!
Osman...
... you will get out of here
only when I want you to.
- Those chains won't be
unlocked until my father returns.
Brother. Brother!
Do you want to go?
- You will drown in your cruelty!
- Shut your mouth!
Bring wine.
My Allah, you don't put a burden
on us that we can't carry.
Give me the wisdom of our mother Sümeyye.
Let me be a martyr like
she was. Give me strength.
When I saw you weeping by the horse...
... I made a promise to myself.
I said whoever upsets this Hatun...
... is my sworn enemy.
Bamsı Bey, unlock me!
Now, before my rage comes to
you like a storm, unlock these locks.
Then lock yourselves there.
- My Bey?
- Hurry! Do as I say. Hurry.
Thank you, Bamsı Bey.
They attacked New Bazaar.
- We should go there at once.
- We should, my valiant, hurry.
Let us go now.
Brave warriors of Catalonia,
I raise my toast for you!
Don't you have a heart?
- A little water.
- You heard Salvador, no water until you talk.
Do you think you came all this way
from Catalonia to make me talk?
- What are you talking about?
- Come, I will tell you.
Come, you are not afraid
of a woman, are you?
Idiot! Does it matter
if a wolf is a he or a she?
- She's getting away!
- Catch the girl, go after him, quickly!
- Catch her!
- Hurry!
Zöhre Hatun.
Bamsı Bey helped Osman
escape from the cage.
He started causing us trouble
even before one of them ended.
- You are trapped.
- I will rip your heads off!
If you try to escape again,
I will break your neck!
Take her.
Osman Bey.
Tursun Bey.
I was also coming to you.
What happened at the New Bazaar,
Tursun Bey?
Bamsı Bey. He's like a father to me,
he knows everything.
They attacked the New Bazaar and
killed everyone.
- Gonca Hatun is injured.
- What about Bala Hatun?
Did something happen to her?
They kidnapped Bala Hatun.
Did they do it?
It's certain who made them do it,
Osman Bey.
But no soldiers left the castle.
They must have found someone to do it.
I don't know who they are.
They probably took her somewhere hidden.
I can't go back to the castle. Once Sofia
sees Bala Hatun, she'll see our connection.
Because she saw Bala Hatun and me
together.
From now on, I'm with you, Osman Bey.
We can only save Bala Hatun from those
killers together.
You'll go to the castle, Tursun Efendi (Mister).
- Why, Bey?
- If they wanted to kill Bala Hatun...
... they would do it in the New Bazaar.
They will want to torture
and question you.
After they can't get any answers from you,
they'll take you to Bala.
Thank you, my Bey. Thank you.
And we will walk all over them.
- Boran.
- Yes, my Bey?
Tursun Efendi will take us to Bala Hatun.
You go after them with Konuralp.
And we...
... will wait for the news at Sergeant
Samsa's Tent.
Your wish is my command, my Bey.
Tell me such things that...
... will make my anger not crumble you.
When they attacked my bazaar in
broad daylight...
... what were you doing, huh?
What were you doing?
There were a lot of them, my Bey. They
came out of nowhere.
Coming out of nowhere, is this.
Are you scarecrows?
Are your swords there just to show off?
Why do I feed you?
Why?
If you don't pay your dues to the food
going down your throat...
... you don't need a throat.
You were asking the other day...
... my Bey, what is your favourite smell?
My bey...
Now I'll answer, Nizamettin Efendi.
The smell of blood.
Don't drop your head.
Now I will ask, and you'll answer.
Okay?
As you command, my Bey.
Even dogs bark when they see an intruder.
Did you bark once, Nizamettin?
What happened to this place?
My bey, please.
We made a mistake, forgive us.
Dump these bodies in the forest.
We couldn't benefit from them, maybe the
wolfs and birds will.
Not with your arm Yökberi, you must pull
with your back. Just like that!
Look, son.
This bow is made from maple.
Under the leather, there is buffalo's
bone.
I wrapped the leather myself.
What I'm trying to say is...
Just for your arrow to hit your target,
many beings died.
A man either puts the bow down or hits
his target.
Now, do you wish the take this bow?
Osman Bey.
Bamsı Bey, friends. Welcome.
Thank you.
If you had informed us, I would kill some
goats for you.
You're not late, Sergeant Samsa.
You have honoured my Tent.
Not just sheep and goats, say the word
and all the beings...
... in these lands shall be sacrificed
for you.
But you don't look like you're here for
a feast.
We'll be your guests for a while,
Sergeant Samsa.
Now we can't relax at our own Tent.
Wish for a Tent, it's there. Wish for a
friend, it's here.
Wish for a pavilion, it's right there.
With great pleasure.
Thank you, Sergeant Samsa.
Get well soon, Alişar Bey.
It won't get well anytime soon,
Dündar Bey.
They attacked the banner lord's bazaar,
no one rests from now on.
I'm a hunter in the woods...
... and you, in the battlefield. Tell me,
who could have done this?
It's certain who the enemies are, and who
the brothers are, Alişar Bey.
Only Kulucahisar could do something
like this.
Any such pillaging could only be
done by Kalonoz.
Kalonoz. Let's see who will save you
from me.
Cowards. Cowards.
My sister, are you okay?
Hatun. Hatun are you okay? Hatun(Woman)!
I am Dündar Bey from Kayı Tent.
Osman Bey's uncle?
I'm his brother Gündüz. What happened?
Tell us.
Tell Osman Bey. They killed everyone.
They kidnapped Bala Hatun.
What does that have to do with Osman Bey?
Who is Bala Hatun?
While they killed everyone, why did
they kidnap Bala Hatun?
A merchant's daughter. What does that have
to do with Osman?
Take her to the Tent. Zöhre Hatun
should treat her.
Then I'll come and find everything out.
Come on now.
I'll find everything out, and you'll be
the first one to hear them, Alişar Bey.
Now it's time to go to the castle
and ask questions.
Be prepared, Dündar Bey. Wait for your
banner lord's word.
War is near.
My Bey. Osman Bey ran away from the Tent
with the Alps(Men).
What are you saying?
He wasn't alone. Bamsı Bey went with them.
Don't let her run away again. Or I will
kill you all!
We have visitors!
Princess Sofia. Welcome.
Catalonia's noble Prince Salvador.
I knew you'd do this so easily.
Prince.
-So this is Edebali's daughter Bala.
- She was a hard case.
Efendi Yannis knows how to break that
case open.
Did anything happen, Princess Sofia?
I know her.
I saw her in the castle dressed as
a sister.
The Priest.
She was with Priest Markus.
What does that mean?
Our church's priest was one of them. He
was Edebali's spy.
Damn it!
He's been in the church for two years.
He tricked us all!
How could they do this?
I will kill them all!
Don't you come close!
Or I'll cut her throat.
Let me go, and I'll let her go.
Bala.
Let me go.
My name is not Bala. You are mixing me up
with someone else.
I don't know any of you! Get back or I'll
kill her!
Bala let me go! This is my final warning!
I said get back!
Don't you remember me, Bala?
You were disguised as a sister when I
last saw you.
The church's priest was with you.
What kind of trickery is this?
I'm a simple merchant's daughter
in the New Bazaar.
And your father is Edebali.
- Get her!
- Get back!
I don't care about death.
- Don't you do it!
- Salvador!
Do it.
Princess Sofia, are you okay?
Salvador, send this snake to
Efendi Yannis.
- Tell him what happened.
- As you wish, Princess Sofia.
Helen, we're going to the castle.
Let's see what kind of a demon is hiding
under Priest Markus' clothes.
Where am I?
Who are you?
Don't worry, Hatun. Don't worry.
You are in good hands, in Kayı Tent.
You were injured. You passed out at
the bazaar.
May Allah bless you all. You took
the trouble.
At least you're alive. Thankfully.
It's an old mark. Looks like it wasn't
your first fight, Hatun.
- Do you use swords?
- Matter of life.
It makes one do such things.
A pack of monsters attacked us.
- Why did they do this?
- How can you look for a reason in them?
It's obvious that they were out raiding.
We're just merchants in the bazaar.
Put ointment on her leg. It should form
a scab.
Put an Alp(man) on her side. She should
not go anywhere.
Alişar Bey.
Did you attack the bazaar, Princess Sofia?
- Welcome.
- I don't feel welcomed.
Tell me. Did they take the attack
orders from you?
Alişar Bey.
You've lived enough in these lands to know
how sensitive the balance is.
Being ignorant isn't enough to do
such a thing.
You also need to be stupid.
Who did it then?
Who is crazy enough to attack my bazaar
in my land?
Alişar Bey. We don't know who
attacked the bazaar.
You know that we wouldn't do such a thing.
Or is there another reason behind you...
... coming to our castle with your
soldiers, your swords, and threatening us?
Whoever is behind this, the only place
they will run to...
... is their death.
Everyone knows that you're the libra
in these lands, Alişar Bey.
If we're on one side of the scale, Kayı
Tent is on the other side.
Did you threaten them like you
are threatening us?
Dündar Bey heard the news about the
attack after it happened, like me.
Besides, why would they do this?
What about Osman?
Did Osman also hear it after it happened?
No one else could have done this.
Why would Osman do it?
The same reason he killed my father for.
That's all he wants. Ending the peace.
He just wants to create a war in
these lands.
Then there is only one way to find out.
We'll go to the Kayı Tent
together, Princess.
Is Osman there?
Osman is in the cage.
It's time to face the facts. The truth
will rise to the surface.
And when God gives them the punishments
they deserve...
... they will see the reason.
Because they are dragged behind
their desires...
... they won't know what being
a human is about.
What do you think you're doing in God's
home. What are you doing here?
God's home, huh? I could kill you with my
bare hands, old man.
With my bare hands!
What do you want from me? I'm an innocent
priest!
An innocent priest, huh?
This is the end of the road,
Priest Markus.
Take him!
Since the day I got my sword...
... my Rab has given me the chance to
fight the evil ones.
I got old. I won't touch another sword,
I said to myself.
But I got back on my feet with my Osman.
My son, my life, my Aybars...
... drank from the shahada sharbat.
And then...
... my soul rose once again.
Osman.
Son, so glad I have you.
So glad I have you, my dark Osman.
Glad I have you.
For your cause, I sacrifice my pavilion,
my Tent, my life, Osman Bey.
I'll run to your orders. I'll
conquer countries.
I'll demolish walls.
Thank you, Sergeant Samsa. Thank you.
Being a friend of such a valiant like you,
is a crown of manhood.
Let's say we have rescued Bala Hatun...
... what about the nation's situation?
Mongolians are wild monsters. The
evilness of Byzantine won't end.
Disorder will burn the Turkish Tents
to the ground.
Dündar Bey gets angry the moment we talk
about a battle.
The age has changed, the times have
changed, Sergeant Samsa.
Now, we'll be bolts of lightning and
dominate the skies without relaxing!
Our swords will get out of their covers,
not to get in ever again.
Whoever follows their desires, will not
be with us.
We'll always be sharp, we'll always be
fresh.
We'll spill the cruel's blood in such
a way that...
... our names will scare all hearts!
I'm the son of Ertuğrul Gazi, Osman.
I swear on the galloping horses
in my blood.
I'll ignite the resurrection fire.
With that fire, I'll burn snakes...
... the fallen ones, and betrayers.
We'll succeed, brothers.
- We'll succeed, if Allah permits.
- We'll succeed son. If Allah permits.
May we come in, Osman Bey?
Come in.
You were right, my Bey.
They caught Tursun.
They threw him in a dungeon. But Boran
brother in on their necks.
Bala Hatun can't be in the dungeon. They
will take him to the uncles.
We need to make their lives
unbearable tomorrow.
But, I hope Boran doesn't
make any mistakes.
Boran brother will inform us once they
take Tursun there.
You...
are the dervish in New Bazaar.
Your father Edebalı was such a wise man...
that he raised a dervish and made him
a priest.
Look at me, you old man!
My father's name isn't Edebalı
and who's the priest?
What are you talking about?
Do you think we don't have
the belief, intelligence...
and courage that your father
has, Bala Hatun (lady)?
I don't know anyone named Bala Hatun!
You and your father were with Ahi Evran
in Kırşehir in some time.
And I was there to become a dervish.
I know your childhood.
I never forget your beautiful eyes
even thousands of years pass, Bala
You're Yannis.
The one who got Mongols killed!
So your father told everything about me.
I know you, Yannis.
-You won't be able to get what you want.
-Don't be so sure.
I serve you death in this plate.
The poison in red bottle
will weaken you...
and make you tell everything.
Then you'll die slowly.
You'll find your cure in blue
bottle whenever you want.
Then I'll set you free.
Don't make me kill a girl that I've
known since her childhood.
No!
-No!
-Open your mouth.
No!
Open your mouth!
Open it!
You're brave like your owner.
You're fearless.
Don't give up.
I'll save you from that swamp.
-My Osman.
-Bamsı Bey.
Come here please.
My Osman...
you look abstracted.
What are you thinking about?
I think that...
whether Tursun draw those devils...
or not.
Son...
are you thinking about...
Tursun or...
Edebalı's daughter?
Both of them.
They will lead us to those cruels' base.
My brave Osman...
now you...
think it's love?
It's love?
Son...
Do you think land means...
just weapon and shield?
Does it mean gallopers?
My Osman, land doesn't just mean tent...
marquee and fluke?
Land means...
love.
It means longing.
It means lover.
How could they endure the pain...
if Oghuz Khan doesn't have
Yar-Su (a nature layer) and...
if Alparslan doesn't have Selcen and...
if Süleyman Shah doesn't have Hayme?
How could they manage to do big issues?
Son...
men are responsible for their horses...
and the valiant is responsible
for his lover.
May my Allah grant us the best.
In sha Allah, we will dupe them.
Tursun resists the tortures.
He resists and we reach our goal.
May Allah give strength to Tursun.
Amin.
No one can save you.
You better start talking.
Even your father can't save you.
Osman...
Osman will save me.
Tell me, Priest Marcus.
Or your name is a lie too?
Stop, for the sake of Holy
Mary. I beg you.
What do you want from me?
I'm a priest!
I serve to God.
Ask everyone!
They know me!
You'll kill me!
I beg you. Don't!
-screaming-
Hasn't he talked yet?
He still says he's Priest Marcus.
I can't wait for an answer.
We have to take possession of Holy
Entrustments and the treasure.
I beg you...
for the sake of our Mother Mary, princess.
Pray with me, Priest Marcus.
Hear my prayers for the sake
of Mother Mary.
God...
hear my prayers.
Answer me with your...
loyalty and integrity.
Do not enter into judgment with your servant...
for in Your sight no one...
living is righteous. (Psalm 143:2)
Princess Sofia...
you know me.
Please believe me.
No!
Edebalı raised him well.
Take him to where Bala Hatun is.
Efendi Yannis (Sir) will make them talk.
Do you think he will?
He never talks even if he dies.
But he will...
for Bala Hatun.
-He lost himself.
-He must be very tired.
His wound will tingle when he wakes up.
Then I'll go to the infirmary and take some herbs.
We'll give him when he wakes up.
Where did Aygül go?
To the infirmary, Mother Zöhre.
He's fevered.
He'll get better, Inshaallah.
Burçin.
Come here.
Since your family died in
Mongol trouble...
you've grown up with me.
You know I see you as my child.
And I see you as my mother, Mother Zöhre.
You're closer to Aygül. You're friends.
She's a bit weird these days.
-What's the problem, Burçin?
-Things happened saddened her.
Burçin.
She hesitates to say.
-But I know.
-Know what?
Aygül loves Osman, Mother Zöhre.
She can't say that.
Can I come in?
Come, Sergeant Samsa.
You bring me food.
You sell grapes.
Are you offended, Sergeant Samsa?
Selling grapes is better
than selling friends.
What's your problem?
You wanted me to stop and not to come.
So?
Are you offended?
You helped.
Your duty is over.
If you had another duty,
Osman Bey would say it.
Konur.
You came as guest. Stay like that.
Or I'll kill you.
I'm not like the others.
I'll harm you.
I'll harm your soul.
What are you doing?
Lower your swords!
Look at them.
Look at them!
You're possessed by the demon!
Sons! When the mountains fall apart,
there occurs a plain...
when they come together, there occurs a
chain of mountains!
My Osman, Osman Bey offers to
resurrect.
But you run wild!
Sons, you need to be a friend to my
Osman.
That is why...
you need to be brothers first.
Now...
now give your blessings to each other
and hug.
Hug each other so that your brotherhood
will be renewed.
Hug each other so that we can
destroy the enemy!
- Give me your blessings.
- You too.
Not like that.
This is not enough.
Sons, our prophet (a.s)
What did he say?
The real wrestlers can keep calm...
even when they are angry.
Now, now you shall kiss each other's
hands.
So that you can hold yourself nex time.
Come on.
We almost were going to fight.
We stopped it, my valiant.
Long live.
Oh, Allah.
- Give me your blessings.
- You too, Sergeant Samsa.
Masha Allah (praise) my valiants!
Son.
Being a leader, being Bey is always hard.
If something bad is to happen...
it may strike at the worst time.
Being a Bey needs responsibility.
In situations like this, in a crisis...
How can I start something as being a
Bey?
How can I capture the hearts?
If you want to be a Bey who is reasonable
and kind...
you need to follow Hz. Muhammed...
Sallā Allāhu ʿalayhi wa-sallam (Peace be upon him)
Our Master created a new civilization
in spite of all those clans...
in the middle of a desert.
Everyone fell apart, he gathered.
He didn't accept cruelty.
He wasn't afraid of the enemy.
He only wanted justice.
What was justice?
there is no god but Allah and...
...Muhammad is the messenger of Allah
They tried everything to
mislead...
the prophet of mercy.
However...
he said: "even if you give me
the moon and sun...
I still won't give up on my case."
They forced him to stop while he
was trying to help people.
He responded kindly.
In Bedir, Uhud, Hendek, the enemy
went mad.
He beat the cruels to their knees.
He clothed the naked like a night.
He enlighted his era like a oil lamp.
He became a light that spread
all over the world.
He was awake while everyone was sleeping.
Everyone fell, he remained standing.
Everyone was tired, he was the hope.
He was the justice.
He was the compassion.
He was the wisdom.
He was the patience.
You should be someone that
when you walk...
justice walks too.
When you smile, compassion will smile.
When you resist, the
patience will stand up.
And people will find the land in you.
And in this land, the light
of our prophet will seem.
May our Allah will make us a great
ummah to our Prophet.
Amin.
My Allah...
grant me and my people...
to establish an empire that...
will spread the light of our Prophet.
What happened in Kulucahisar in the night
that Governor Yorgopolos died?
You killed Yorgopolos.
He had to die.
We're not killers.
Burn in hell, you devil.
How did you learn that I hid
the Holy Entrustments...
in the Kulucahisar?
You won't learn...
anything from me.
Osman Bey is with Edebalı.
What about Ertuğrul Bey?
Who's in it other than Kayıs?
Neither Osman Bey nor Kayıs...
know about anything.
The night you killed Governor...
he came to where Governor is...
to chase the murderer
of his blood brother.
Calm down.
Calm down. Calm.
Kerem and Aslı.
You try hardly to keep Osman away
from a devil like me.
I see fear in your eyes for him.
Those beautiful eyes says that you're
in love with Osman Bey.
You old man!
I'm telling you the truth.
Osman Bey...
doesn't know our secret.
He doesn't.
So Osman caught up in
it without knowing.
It doesn't matter. He'll die
soon or later.
The Alps (men) in his tent and...
all Turks that occupied
our lands will die!
As to you...
you can live...
if I want to.
Or you'll tell me where the
Holy Entrustments are.
The death...
is our salvation.
Shahada is our meeting.
I'm patient, Bala.
I'll watch you dying.
You'll see that you can't
hide secrets from me.
Bi-smi llāhi r-raḥmāni r-raḥīm ("In the name of God, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful"
Quran Al-Masad ("The Palm Fiber") [111]
"May the hands of Abu Lahab
be ruined, and ruined is he."
"His wealth will not avail
him or that which he gained."
"He will [enter to] burn in
a Fire of [blazing] flame"
"And his wife [as well]
- the carrier of firewood."
"Around her neck
is a rope of [twisted] fiber."
What did she say, sir?
She prayed.
In the name of Allah, the
Most Beneficent, the Most Merciful.
The hands of Abu Lahab
were ruined, and ruined was he."
He couldn't make use of his wealth
and he didn't gain anything.
He'll go to hell.
Although his wife has a rope
made from twisted fiber
she will go to hell, carrying the firewood.
Her faith won't save her from
my poison. She'll talk.
Sir...
They killed our friends.
We're given out.
Sir...
Bala Hatun...
They abducted her.
My daughter.
Gonca Hatun is wounded.
Dündar Bey took her to Kayı
Tent for the treatment.
Friends...
We aren't counted by fingers...
We aren't given out
For the land, not one child...
but thousand of children are sacrificed.
My Allah who saves İbrahim
from the fire...
İsmail from the knife and...
Yusuf from wellholes, Yunus
in from floods...
and Prophet in caves.
You protect our secret.
Keep my daughter's head up.
Give her strength.
Give her Hz. Ayşe's wisdom...
Hz. Fatima's courage...
and Hz. Sümeyye's patience.
Make us tough against heathens.
Make our weapons strong, make
our horses strong.
Make our valiants victorious.
Make the enemy defeated.
Undoubtfully, victory is yours.
My Bey(chief), they have been trapped.
We got them.
- Where are they?
- They are on the way to Nika.
- Eternal Allah!
Allah is one!
Hi.
What's the matter, Efendi (sir).
You are a dervish. Why are you checking
weapons?
Carrying a weapon is sunnah.
So, I am doing just like that.
Eyvallah.
(Fair enough)
Also, since Ertuğrul Bey went to Konya...
There has been no peace.
We hear bazaar raids, caravan raids
every day.
You are right Dervish.
Now, there is no peace here.
They raided the new bazaar near the lake
also.
I heard that everybody was killed.
Is this true?
It is true, Dervish.
Their identities are unclear.
- They killed everyone.
- Was there no one left alive?
Just a wounded girl survived.
And Dündar Bey took her to the tent.
How is the Hatun (Lady)?
She is in the infirmary.
Zülha Hatun is taking care of her.
She will be okay, in sha Allah.
But, why are you asking?
Healing comes from Allah, but we can
pray, at least.
O Allah, The healer
In fact, her heal is in my hands.
We could welcome you better if you had
sent a messenger.
We would offer you sherbet and meat
abundantly.
Everybody knows how Kayıs are generous
in the table, Dündar Bey.
We came to talk, not to eat.
You are too crowded for just talking.
However, our home is enough for everyone.
Let's go inside.
Princess Sofia has sent the priest,
Efendi (sir).
What do you want from me?
Who is that girl?
I want you to save this nun, priest.
Which nun?
Look at her face.
Look closer, you'll recognize her.
One of the two nuns who were wandering
with you.
This is a Turkish girl.
Not a nun at all.
What are you looking for?
I don't know this girl.
Just kill her, I don't care.
She is a Turk anyways.
Let me go in the name of god.
You are committing a huge sin.
- What was that?
- Poison.
What are you doing?
This a pill that makes her talk about
everything she knows.
If she doesn't talk, a slow and painful
death is waiting for her.
God forgive this girl's sins.
If you don't want her to die, you need to
tell us where Edebali's treasure is.
I have a cure that can heal her.
If you give me what I want, I'll let
both of you live.
- So, you'll have forgiven her.
- Who are you?
Monk Yannis, from Margarit Abbey.
My Alps (men) are in the position.
They are waiting for your sign.
If we raid, they will kill both Bala Hatun
and Tursun.
- Son, what are you talking about?
- Bala Hatun and Tursun are inside.
We need to infiltrate so that they don't
get hurt.
Let's go.
Demirbüken, Aykut.
Wait here.
Now, tell me.
What is the reason that made you come
here, Kayı tent?
Justice, Dündar Bey.
So as not to lose contact and damage
our friendship that you built.
This is a friendly visit.
There are several issues damaging
our good relations, Dündar Bey.
That my daughter has been abducted and
brought to your castle is one of them, right?
Of course.
No one would want this to happen.
But, don't forget.
All of this is up to...
Osman.
We intend to solve this problem
without causing any harm, Dündar Bey.
We want to face Osman and ask him our
questions in Alişer Bey's supervision.
This is the best way.
Also, this would hamper the ones who
want to set us against each other.
Call Osman.
Osman is not here.
What do you mean?
They told me that he was in the cage.
He had a problem with Batur.
I commanded to send him into the cage.
But he escaped.
How can't you take care of a criminal...
who is accused of so many crimes,
Gündüz Bey?
How could he escape under all those Alps'
(men) supervision.
Just like how he escaped
from your...
castle's dungeon, in your command,
Kalanoz.
It's obvious you did that before we face
Osman.
Are you playing with us?
This is a reason for war, Dündar Bey!
Kalanoz, when we are born...
before our names,
they whisper "war" into our ears
The one who is afraid of fighting is vile!
How can a monk like you...
so relentless, Yannis?
Let me go, I beg you.
I am Priest Marcus.
You can investigate.
Everyone knows me.
I am Priest Marcus.
Enough, enough.
Megela!
So, you decided to talk.
Kill him, I don't care.
Kill me too.
Let this end.
I don't know where holy entrustment is.
Only my father knows that.
Maybe if you die...
he'll speak.
God, give me strength.
Bala Hatun.
Bala Hatun ha?
Your identity is revealed, priest.
Or should I call you "Edebali's spy"?
You are a devil, Yannis.
We don't know where holy entrustment is.
You can never learn what we don't know.
You can't stop the words of Allah.
You can't stop Turks' awakening and
their foundation.
The wood sword will find its owner.
That day will be your end!
Allah is the greatest!
Let's do it son.
It's time.
We are ready, my Bey (chief).
It's a raid!
Raid!
Come on my valiants, get them all!
Allah is eternal!
Sergeant Samsa, Bamsı Bey(chief)
go that way.
Osman is coming!
Osman...
- Damn it.
- Sir, what are we going to do?
Osman...
Come with me, Megela.
Bala.
Bala, Bala, Bala.
No.
No, no.
Bala.
Bala, bala, open your eyes.
I'm here.
I'm with you.
Tursun, Tursun, Tursun!
Thank Allah, he is alive.
Osman Bey(chief) Edebali's daughter
Bala Hatun...
will die achingly and slowly
in three days.
Only I have her cure.
If you want to save her,
give me what you stole from me back.
Efendi (sir) Yannis.
Bala.
Open your eyes, open!
Let your eyes kill me.
Let them destroy me.
I just need you to open your eyes.
Bala.
- Osman.
- Bala.
You came for me.
Yeah, I came for you.
I will never leave you again.
You... know it...
it is... too late....
Ya- Yannis' poison... is in my blood.
I'll find that Yannis even if he
goes to hell.
I'll come back with your cure.
Do not do it.
Don't.
You... are... hope...
for... the... people... Osman.
It's... not.... worth.... for....
a... Bala.
For a Bala, Kulucahisar aside, ...
I'd burn the whole universe.
I'll find your cure and come back.
Don't give up.
Think of your father.
Think of your Ahi (the Ahi Brotherhood)
brothers.
I'd sacrifice my every breath for you.
Don't give up.
Do not give up.
Give me...
your... blessings... Osman.
Bala.
Bala, Bala, Bala!
Bala, open your eyes, Bala.
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah she is alive.
When two lovers come together, they
must be happy.
Be happy.
You are entrusted to Allah.
Goodbye.
I didn't like that man.
Neither the traitors nor the cruels
stop.
We just need to be honest.
Find a stretcher for
Bala Hatun and Tursun.
Take them to my father's tent.
Bala Hatun is entrusted to my Ayşe Aunt.
- Do what is necessary.
- Of course, my Bey (chief).
- They poisoned Bala Hatun.
- Devils.
They have the cure.
What do they want, my Bey?
We are not going to give,
we are going to take!
Sofia's life in exchange for
Bala Hatun's life!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com